Shaun Samoridny

ssamoridny@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/shaun-samoridny/ https://github.com/SSamoridny (780)952-0432 Edmonton, AB, Canada

Profile

As a life long learner I bring a desire to create, grow and always strive for more. Not content with the status quo I decided to make a massive jump, bet on myself and become a Full Stack Web Developer. In my 30+ years in the workforce, I have cultivated great personal and professional relationships where I am always doing my best to elevate those around me. I promise I will bring that same enthusiasm and dedication to your company and become an integral part of your team.

Experience

ACCOUNT EXECUTIVE, CITRON HYGIENE - OCT 2019 - JUL 2020

- Responsible for prospecting new territories from scratch to build a strong sales funnel through cold calling and call blocking with a hunter mentality
- Accomplished in using research and presentation skills to qualify and close potential new customers across all possible industries
- Creation and execution of sales plans and goals using Salesforce CRM

SALES REPRESENTATIVE, CINTAS FIRST AID AND SAFETY – AUG 2018 - OCT 2019

- Responsible for opening the Edmonton market to Cintas First Aid and Safety in a remote sales role
- Excelled in creating new business from scratch via Microsoft Dynamics
- Helped the Western Canadian division surpass expectations by over 32% and helped Edmonton receive a brick and mortar location in our first year of operation

INSIDE SALES & MARKETING COORDINATOR, RBW GROUP – JUN 2017 - AUG 2018 TERRITORY MANAGER EDMONTON EAST, RBW GROUP - APR 2006 - JUN 2017

- Leader of a cross-functional team implementing inbound marketing strategies while saving our company costs through an internal team approach
- Responsible for creating and executing inside sales and distribution plans for 1000+ clients to achieve revenue targets

- Responsible for the planning and implementation of sales and marketing strategies with our outside sales team to convey a consistent message and image for the RBW Group
- Presided over a territory consisting of over \$1,500,000 in sales annually
- Delivered a CAGR of over 10% while functioning in a distressed financial market for our consumers in the oil and gas industry

Education

University of Toronto SCS – Full Stack Web Development 2020

Tan Stack Tree Bereiopinent 202

MacEwan University – Management Studies 2002

Certificates

Requirements Based Selling (02/2019)

Challenger Sales Certification (10 / 2019)

Codecademy Pro Intensive (08 / 2017)

Hubspot Inbound Certification (12/2017)

Skills

JavaScript / Node.JS / MySQL / MVC / Express / Bootstrap / HTML / CSS / Leadership / Team Oriented / Networking / Customer Service / Goal Setting and Planning / Relationship Building / Oral and Written Communication / Presenting

Soft Skills

Adaptable / Creative / Detail Oriented / Emotionally Intelligent / Enthusiastic / Genuine Character / Honesty / Leadership / Strong Work Ethic / Time Management / Confident / Competitive / Eternal Optimism / Desire to Grow through Education and Learning / Determination and Grit / Desire to Achieve